* [US](javascript:void(0))

[](javascript:void(0))

Choose your country or region

Mobvoi Privacy Policy
=====================

### Mobvoi Privacy Policy

##### Last Updated: September 29, 2022 (This Policy will be taken effect as of May 26, 2020)

Thank you for using Mobvoi!

Your privacy is important to us. Mobvoi respects your right to privacy. This Privacy Policy explains who we are, how we collect, share and use personal information about you, and how you can exercise your privacy rights. This Privacy Policy applies to personal information that we collect through Mobvoi app, TicWatch series devices, Tichome series smart loudspeakers manufactured by Mobvoi (collectively referred as "**Mobvoi services**" or "**services of Mobvoi**").

If your Mobvoi services are provided in English language, then currently operation system is powered by **Wear OS by Google (formerly as Android Wear)**. Mobvoi does not own or control Wear OS by Google and when you interact with them, you may be providing information directly to Wear OS by Google and other third parties of their choosing. These third parties will have their own rules about the collection, use and disclose of information. We encourage you to review their privacy policies.

When this Policy mentions "Mobvoi", "We", "Us", or "Our", it refers to the Mobvoi Information Technology Company Limited that is responsible for your information under this Privacy Policy (the "**Data Controller**").

If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your personal information, then please contact us using the contact details provided at the bottom of this Privacy Policy.

#### Quick links

We recommend that you read this Privacy Policy in full to ensure you are fully informed. However, if you only want to access a particular section of this Privacy Policy, then you can click on the relevant link below to jump to that section.

[1\. What Does Mobvoi Do](#mobvoiDo) [2\. Legal Basis for Processing Personal Information](#mobvoiLegal) [3\. How We Collect Your Personal Information](#mobvoiPersonal) [4\. How We Use Your Personal Information](#mobvoiUse) [5\. How We Share, Transfer, Publically Disclose and Retain Your Personal Information](#mobvoiShare) [6\. How We Protect Your Personal Information](#mobvoiProtect) [7\. Your Rights to Manage the Personal Information](#mobvoiManage) [8\. Our Notice](#mobvoiNotice) [9\. Third Party Partners & Integrations](#mobvoiPartner) [10\. Data Retention](#mobvoiRetention) [11\. Global Operations and International Data Transfers](#mobvoiOperation) [12\. How We Use Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies](#mobvoiCookie) [13\. How We Dispose the Personal Information of Children](#mobvoiDispose) [14\. Privacy Policy Update](#mobvoiPrivacy) [15\. How to Contact Us](#mobvoiContact)

#### 1\. What Does Mobvoi Do

Mobvoi Information Technology Company Limited and all [affiliated companies](https://www.mobvoi.com/asia/pages/affiliate-notice) is an artificial intelligence company, headquartered in Beijing, P.R. China, but with group companies all around the world. Our Services based on core voice-based technologies enable Mobvoi and our authorised partner to serve you with personalised life assistant service through human-computer interaction.

For more information about Mobvoi, please see the "About Us" section of our Website at [https://www.mobvoi.com/pages/about-us.](https://www.mobvoi.com/pages/about-us)

#### 2\. Legal Basis for Processing Personal Information

If you are a visitor from the European Economic Area, our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.

However, we will normally collect personal information from you only (i) where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you, (ii) where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your rights, or (iii) where we have your consent to do so. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you or may otherwise need the personal information to protect your vital interests or those of another person.

If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contact with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information).

If we collect and use your personal information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), this interest will normally be to operate our platform and communicating with you as necessary to provide our services to you and for our legitimate commercial interest, for instance, when responding to your queries, improving our platform, undertaking marketing, or for the purposes of detecting or preventing illegal activities. We may have other legitimate interests and if appropriate we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.

If you have questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your personal information, please contact us using the contact details provided under the "[How to contact us](#mobvoiContact)".

#### 3\. How We Collect Your Personal Information

**When you use the services of Mobvoi, we ask for and collect the following your personal information.**

1. **3.1 Information that you provide voluntarily**
    
    For using Mobvoi services, we may ask you to provide personal information voluntarily. The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information. You do not have to provide your personal information to Mobvoi, but in some cases, the non-provision of certain personal information will cause the inability to provide you with some related products or services.
    
    **Information that is necessary for the use of the Mobvoi services**
    
    **This information is necessary for the adequate performance of the services provided by Mobvoi. Without it, we may not be able to provide you with all the services requested by you.**
    
    * **Account Information.** When you sign up a Mobvoi account, we require certain information such as name, phone number and/or email address, contact information.
    
    **Personal Information you choose to share with us**
    
    **You may choose to provide us with additional personal information in order to have a better user experience when using services of Mobvoi. This additional information will be processed based on your consent.**
    
    **We kindly remind you that when you use TicWatch S&E series, such information will be provided to Wear OS by Google and you will be informed in time when Wear OS by Google and other Google apps ask for your personal information.**
    
    * **Additional profile information.** You may choose to provide additional information as part of your Mobvoi profile (such as gender, photo, nickname, Date of Birth, common address, and mailing address).
    * **Your physiological information.** You may choose to provide your information on physiological feature, sports and health when you using the Fitness app, Health app, Heart Rate app, Step Ranking app and some dial plates, such us your height, weight, step number, calorie consumed, sports mode (i.e. running or walking) and walking distance.
    * **Reminder on SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION.** Some of the personal information that you provide may include sensitive personal information, such as your personal health information; such information is more strictly regulated than other types of personal information. Before providing any “sensitive” personal information to us, please clearly consider whether it is appropriate.You agree that your sensitive personal information may be processed in accordance with the purposes and methods described in this Privacy Policy. You of course have the rights to control, please see **[Section 7 Your Rights to Manage the Personal Information.](#mobvoiManage)**
    * **Share Information** refers to your information or information related to you shared voluntarily on Mobvoi services. The share information can include the information you posted on Mobvoi accounts (including your publicized personal information, your Mobvoi account name, and Mobvoi account user photo, Bluetooth, video and recording obtained from the camera and/or radio sensor in your device with your prior consent). The share information also includes the information related to you shared by other users who use the services of Mobvoi (including location data and log information).
2. **3.2 Information we automatically collect from your use of the Services of Mobvoi**
    
    When you use the services of Mobvoi, we automatically collect the following your information from your device. In some countries, including countries in EEA, this information may be considered personal information under applicable data protection laws.
    
    Specifically, the information we collect automatically may include information like your IP address, device type, unique device identification numbers, browser-type, broad geographic location (e.g. country or city-level location), contact information and other technical information. We may also collect information about how your device has interacted with our website, including the pages accessed and links clicked.
    
    Collecting these types of information enables us to better understand the users. We use this information to analyse your preference, habit and location, etc. so as to provide more tailored services to you (e.g. accurately record your movement trajectory and provide advertising and promotion information that better meets your needs).
    
    This information is necessary for the adequate performance of our contractual obligation to enable us to comply with legal obligations and given our legitimate interest in being able to provide and improve the functionalities of services of Mobvoi.
    
    * **Location Information.** The location of the device when you are using the products of Mobvoi, such as GPS, wifi, compass, accelerometer or other sensors used by your mobile devices. Internet protocol address (IP address) of the device or Internet service you used to access the services of Mobvoi. We will ask you to choose the applications for which you want to enable location services. In the device settings menu, you can disable the location permissions of specific services to reject sharing your location information.
    * **Log Information.** The location of the device when you are using the products of Mobvoi, such as GPS, wifi, compass, accelerometer or other sensors used by your mobile devices. Internet protocol address (IP address) of the device or Internet service you used to access the services of Mobvoi. We will ask you to choose the applications for which you want to enable location services. In the device settings menu, you can disable the location permissions of specific services to reject sharing your location information.[](https://www.mobvoi.com/asia/pages/cookie-policy)
    * **Technical information.** We automatically collect such as information related to your mobile operator, your web browser or the setting information you provided to access other programs of Mobvoi, your IP address and the version and identification number of your device (e.g. IMEI number and Android ID);
    * **Communication information by Mobvoi.**Communication information by Mobvoi.
3. **3.3 Information that we obtain from third party**
    
    From time to time, we may receive personal information about you from third party sources (including Google etc.), but only where we have checked that these third parties either have your consent or are otherwise legally permitted to disclose your personal information to us.
    
    The types of information we collect from third parties include account information and we use the information we receive from these third parties to create/sign up Mobvoi account and maintain and improve the accuracy of the records we hold about you.
    
    These third parties will have their own rules about the collection, use and disclose of information. We encourage you to review their privacy policies.
    
4. **3.4 Collection and use of non-identifiable data**
    
    Non-identifiable data refers to data that cannot be used to identify an individual. Examples of non-identifiable data include statistics on website visits, application downloads, and product sales volume. Mobvoi will collect statistics information to understand how users use our products and services. By doing so, we can improve our services to better meet your requirements.  
    We keep your personal information and non-identifiable data separate, and use each independently. Circumstances may arise where Mobvoi collects, uses, discloses, and transfers non-identifiable data for other purposes at our own discretion.

#### 4\. How We Use Your Personal Information

**We use, store, and process your information, including your personal information, to provide, understand, improve, and develop our Services of Mobvoi, create and maintain a trusted and safer environment and comply with our legal obligations.  
  
If you use a smart watch when you go out and ask, you will provide us with your height, weight, age, number of steps, calories burned, your exercise mode (for example, running or walking), and distance traveled. Regarding health data, you will provide us with your heart rate, body temperature, blood oxygen, respiration rate, HRV, sleep information, etc.**

1. **4.1 Provide, improve and develop Mobvoi Services**
    
    * For providing the services of Mobvoi (and specific function within services of Mobvoi). For example, you can make Bluetooth calls in the software of Mobvoi and display relevant contents based on your location.
    * For providing logistics delivery, order inquiry, after-sales service relating to services as you purchased our products via online store.
    * For sharing your personal information between Mobvoi services. The collected personal information when you use Mobvoi devices can be used in another Mobvoi device to provide you with specific content. You can also request us, from time to time, to transfer or transmit the stored personal information between Mobvoi services (if available).
    
    We process this information given our legitimate interest in improving Mobvoi services with it, and where it is necessary for the adequate performance of the contract with you.
    
2. **4.2 Create and maintain a safer environment**
    
    * For customer service, security, fraud detection, archive and backup purposes as we provide the services of Mobvoi which in line with [Mobvoi Terms of Service](https://www.mobvoi.com/asia/pages/terms-of-service) and other Mobvoi policies.
    * Comply with our legal obligations.
    
    We process this information given out legitimate interest in protecting services of Mobvoi to measure the adequate performance of our contract with you and to comply with applicable laws.
    
3. **4.3 Provide, customise, measure and improve our advertising and marketing**
    
    * For the better understanding how you access and use the services of Mobvoi, improving the services of Mobvoi and developing new services; and for responding to users’ wishes and preference, including language setting, location setting, personalised support services and instructions; or for giving other responses to you and other Mobvoi services users.
    * For product presentation, personalised recommendations and sending promotional information, such as airplane/train journey, cinema film schedule, regional weather alteration message, and interested news/topics, etc.
    
    We will process your personal information for the purposes listed in this section given our legitimate interest in undertaking marketing activities to offer you products or services that may be of your interest. You can opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us by following the unsubscribe instructions included in our marketing communications or changing your notification settings within your Mobvoi Account.
    
4. 4.4 In general, we will use the personal information we collect from you only for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or for purposes that we explain to you at the time we collect your personal information. However, we may also use your personal information for other purposes that are not incompatible with the purposes we have disclosed to you, we will ask for your consent in advance or if for archiving purposes in the public interest, scientific or historical research purposes, or statistical purposes and where this is permitted by applicable data protection laws where published in the relevant jurisdictions.
    
5. 4.5 The agreement or clauses relating to use personal information in [Mobvoi Terms of Service](https://www.mobvoi.com/asia/pages/terms-of-service), if any, is still subject to this Privacy Policy.

#### 5\. How We Share, Transfer, Publically Disclose and Retain Your Personal Information

We do not share personal information with other companies, organizations and individuals unless one of the following circumstances applies:

**5.1 Sharing with consent**

After obtaining your consent, Mobvoi will share the information that you have authorized with specified third parties or categories of third parties.

**5.2 Sharing pursuant to laws and regulations**

* Share your personal information to any **competent law enforcement body, regulatory, government agency, court or other third party** where we believe disclosure is necessary (i) as a matter of applicable law or regulation, (ii) to exercise, establish or defend our legal rights, (iii) to protect your vital interests or those of any other person; or (iv) to pursue our legitimate interests where your rights and freedoms do not outweigh these interests.

**5.3 Our affiliated companies**

To enable or support us in providing services of Mobvoi, we may share your information, including personal information, within our [corporate affiliates](https://www.mobvoi.com/asia/pages/affiliate-notice). We only share the necessary personal information and we are bound by the purpose stated in the Privacy Policy. If the affiliated companies change the purpose of processing personal information, they will ask for your re-authorization and re-consent. Leanr more about our affiliates [here](https://www.mobvoi.com/asia/pages/affiliate-notice). The data sharing is necessary for the performance of the contract between you and us.

* We may share some of your personal information with our partners to perform a contract with you. Service providers may be located inside or outside of the European Economic Area (“EEA”). In particular, our service providers are based in Europe, India, Asia Pacific and North America.
* We will share your necessary information to service providers that support our worldwide business for the following purposes: 1) Assisting us in providing the services of Mobvoi for you; 2) Assisting us in performing the purpose stated in「**[How We Use Your Personal Information](#mobvoiUse)**」section; 3) Fulfilling our responsibilities and enforce our rights under the [Mobvoi Terms of Service](https://www.mobvoi.com/asia/pages/terms-of-service) or this Privacy Policy and/or assist in understanding and improving our services; and 4) Provide the technical infrastructure service, analyse the usage mode of our services, measure the effectiveness of advertisement, services and payment convenience, or conduct academic research and survey.
* For example, suppliers who need your delivery address to arrange delivery; communication service providers who sends E-mail or push notice on our behalf.
* We will only share your personal information for legitimate, reasonable, necessary, specific, and explicit purposes. And we will only share the necessary personal information to provide services. These providers have limited access to your information to perform these tasks on our behalf and are contractually bound to protect and to use it only for the purposes for which it was disclosed and consistent with this Privacy Policy.

**5.5 Authorised advertising and analysis service partners.**

Only if obtaining your consent, we will not share your personal information with the partners who provide advertisement and analysis service. We will provide these partners with information about their advertising coverage and effectiveness without providing your personal identifiable information, or we may aggregate this information so that it does not identify your identity. For example, if advertisers agree to comply with our advertising guidelines, we may provide feedback about the effect, audience population of the advertisement or the number of people affected by the advertisement to install apps, or non-personal-identifiable demographic information (such as "25-year-old male in France with software development habit ") to assist them understand their audience or customers.

**5.6 Business transfers**

If Mobvoi undertakes or is involved in any merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of assets, bankruptcy or insolvency event, then we may sell, transfer or share some or all of our assets, including your information in connection with such transaction or in contemplation of such transaction (e.g. due diligence). In this event, we will require the new companies or organisations that hold your personal information to continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy, otherwise we will require the companies or the organisations to ask for your re-authorisation and re-consent.

**5.7 Aggregated data.**

We may also share aggregated information (information about our users that we combine together so that it no longer identifies or references an individual user) and other anonymised information for regulatory compliance, industry and market analysis, demographic profiling, marketing and advertising, and other business purposes.

**5.8 Reminder on processing personal information with third parties**

If we or our affiliated companies must share your personal information with any third party to help us provide and improve our Services. We also impose strict restrictions on how our partners can use and disclose the data we provide. For example, we will sign a strict confidentiality agreement with that third party and we will use reasonable efforts to ensure the third party to use your personal information only under the following circumstances: (i) comply with this Privacy Policy; And (ii) subject to any other instruction we issued to such third party, including any our implemented appropriate confidentiality and security measure. We may provide these partners with aggregated and anonymised information, or other non-personal-identifiable information.

#### 6\. How We Protect Your Personal Information

6.1 We have taken the safety protection measures which conform to the industry standard to protect your personal information that we collect and process about you, and prevent data from suffering from unauthorized visit, public disclosure, usage, modification, damage or loss. The measures we use are designed to provide a level of security appropriate to the risk of processing your personal information. For example, when you exchange data (such as credit card information) between your browser and “service”, it is protected by SSL encryption; We provide Https-safe browsing way for the website appeared in the homepage of the Privacy Policy; We use the encryption technology to ensure the confidentiality of data; We use the reliant protection mechanism to prevent data from suffering from malicious attack; We deploy the access control mechanism to ensure only authorized person can access the personal information; And we hold the safety and privacy protection training course to strengthen the recognition of our personnel about the importance of personal information protection.

6.2 In the case of a personal information breach, Mobvoi as data controller is under a legal obligation to notify the supervisory authority without undue delay (normally within 72 hours) unless the breach is unlikely to result in a risk to the rights and freedoms of the individuals.

6.3 We take all reasonable and feasible measures to ensure not to collect irrelevant personal information. We will only reserve your personal information to achieve the purpose stated in the Privacy Policy within the period required, unless such period need permitted by laws to be extended.

6.4 The internet is not an absolutely secure environment, and the email, instant messaging and other forms of communication with other Mobvoi users are not encrypted. We therefore strongly recommend that you do not to send the confidential information in this way. Please use a complicated password to secure your account.

6.5 We will make our best effort to ensure the security of any information you send as the internet environment is not absolutely secure. In the unfortunate event of a personal information security incident, we will promptly inform you in accordance with the requirements of laws and regulations, including the basic situation of such incident, its possible impact, the treatment measures we have taken or will take, suggestions on how to prevent and reduce risks and remedial measures for you, etc. We will timely inform you of the relevant situation of events by E-mail, letter, telephone and pushing notice. If there is any difficult to inform the personal information owner individually, we will take reasonable and effective ways to issue an announcement. Meanwhile, in accordance with the requirements of the regulatory authorities, we will actively report such authorities the development of the personal information security events.

#### 7\. Your Rights to Manage the Personal Information

Legislation in some countries and regions to which Mobvoi provides products and services or from where Mobvoi processes personal information, provides that data subjects the rights request in regard to the accessing, rectifying, deleting or erasure, porting, restricting, and objecting, the processing of related personal information by Mobvoi retains. In addition you will have the right to data portability.

**7.1 Right of access**

You have right to access your personal information except for prohibited by laws and regulations. If you want to exercise the access right, you can access it per se in following ways:

1. a) **Account information** -- you can access or edit the personal data information and payment information in your account, change your password, add safety information or close your account, etc. You can perform such operations by accessing 【Mobvoi App → User Center】.
2. b) **Search information** -- you can access 【Mobvoi App → User Center】 to access or clear your search history, view and edit your interests and manage other data.

If you cannot access this personal information through above links or you wish to access information about you that are not provided on the links above, you can send E-mail to support@mobvoi.com and we will reply your access request without undue delay and in any event within one month of receipt of the request.

We will provide other personal information to you that arises from your use of our products or services, only if it is not overmuch time-consuming. If you want to exercise data access, please send an email to support@mobvoi.com.

**7.2 Right to rectification**

If you find there is an inaccurate or incomplete personal information when we are processing your personal information, you have right to require us to correct it. You can correct it on your own through 【Mobvoi App → User Center】.

If you cannot correct this personal information through above links, you can send E-mail to support@mobvoi.com to file a correction request. We will process your correction request without undue delay and in any event within one month of receipt of the request.

**7.3 Right to erasure ('Right to be Forgotten')**

In the following circumstances, you can request us to delete your personal information:

1. a) If we process personal information in violation of laws and regulations;
2. b) If we collect and use your personal information without your consent;
3. c) If we process personal information in violation of our agreement;
4. d) If you no longer use our products and services, or you cancel your Mobvoi account;
5. e) If Mobvoi no longer serves you.

You can make a request to erasure your personal information by sending E-mail to support@mobvoi.com and we will reply your request without undue delay and in any event within one month of receipt of the request.

When you delete the information from Mobvoi services, we may not immediately delete the corresponding information from the backup system; we will yet delete such information when the backup system is scheduled on updates.

7.4 In addition, you can **object to processing** of your personal information, ask us to **restrict processing** of your personal information or **request portability** of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by sending E-mail to support@mobvoi.com and we will reply your request without undue delay and in any event within one month of receipt of the request.

**7.5 Change the scope of your authorization and consent**

Each business function requires some basic personal information to be completed (see [Section 3](#mobvoiPersonal) of this Privacy Policy). You may give or withdraw your consent at any time of the collection and use of your personal information other than minimums use/set. You can perform such operations by accessing 【Enter personal phone settings → select to close the services of Mobvoi】.

When you withdraw your consent, we will not process the corresponding personal information. However, your decision to withdraw consent will not affect personal information processing based on your previous authorization, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

**7.6 Right to out-put of marketing communications**we send you at any time.

You can exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in the marketing e-mails we send you. To opt-out of other forms of marketing (such as postal marketing or telemarketing), then please contact us using the contact details provided under the "[,How to contact us](#mobvoiContact)".

**7.7 Right to data portability**

You have the right to obtain your personal information copy. You can perform such operations by sending E-mail to support@mobvoi.com, and we will process your request without undue delay and in any event within one month of receipt of the request.

If technology measures permit, such as the data interface is compatible, we can also send a copy of your personal information to your designated third party directly at your request.

**7.8 Right to complaint**

You have right to compliant a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority

**7.9 How we respond to your request**

To protect the security, you may need to provide the request in written or in other ways for your identity verification, then we can proceed. For your request, we will reply without undue delay and in any event within one month of receipt of the request.

In principle, we do not charge of your reasonable requests. However, we will charge a certain amount of cost for the requests that are repeated multiple times and exceed reasonable limits. We may reject requests if it is unreasonably repeated or requires overmuch time-consuming technical approach (such as a need to develop new systems or fundamentally change current practices) or poses a risk to the others legal rights and interests or is unrealistic (such as involving information stored on backup tapes/hard disks).

#### 8\. Our Notice

**8.1 Notices and other types of communications**

When you use the Mobvoi service, we can use your personal information to send emails, text messages, or push notifications to your device. If you do not wish to receive these newsletters, you can choose to have the "Cancellation Notice" (if any) on your device or contact us at support@mobvoi.com .

**8.2 Service-related announcements**

We may from time to time send you service-related announcements in necessary (for example, when we suspend the Mobvoi service for maintenance). You are not entitled to cancel such announcements as it is service-related but not promotion-related.

#### 9\. Third Party Partners & Integrations

Mobvoi services may contain links to third party websites or services, such as third party integrations, co-branded services, or third party-branded services ("**Third Party Partners**"). Mobvoi doesn’t own or control these Third Party Partners and when you interact with them, you may be providing information directly to the Third Party Partner, Mobvoi, or both. These Third Party Partners will have their own rules about the collection, use, and disclosure of information. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of the other websites you visit.

**Related system permissions**  
If your device is an iPhone, when you need to display the sports health data from Mobvoi in the Health app of your iPhone, the system will request your authorization to write the data into the Health Kit. If you do not agree or cancel the authorization, it will not be the corresponding data will be displayed again, but it will not affect your use of other functions of Mobvoi products and services. We will not share or sell the data obtained from HeathKit to any third party, including advertisers and other agencies, nor use HeathKit's information for marketing, advertising, data mining or other similar purposes.

#### 10\. Data Retention

We retain personal information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal, tax or accounting requirements).

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymise it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

#### 11\. Global Operations and International Data Transfers

We operate globally to bring you our services. Where the laws of your country allow you to do so, you authorise us to transfer, store, and use your personal data in the United States, Mainland China and any other country where we operate. In some of the countries to which we transfer personal data, the privacy and data protection laws and rules regarding when government authorities may access data may vary from those of your country.

Specifically, our servers are located in Mainland China, and our group companies and third party service providers and partners operate around the world. This means that when we collect your personal information we may process it in any of these countries.

When we transfer personal data outside of the EEA, we ensure an adequate level of protection for the rights of data subjects based on the adequacy of the receiving country’s data protection laws, contractual obligations placed on the recipient of the data (model clauses may be requested by inquiry as described below), or EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield principles.

**Mobvoi has implemented global privacy practices for processing personal information protected under various data protection laws. Mobvoi transfers personal information between the countries in which we operate in accordance with the standards and conditions of applicable data protection laws, including standards and conditions related to security and processing.**

**Our Standard Contractual Clauses can be provided on request by sending email to support@mobvoi.com. We have implemented similar appropriate safeguards with our third party service providers and partners and further details can be provided upon request.**

#### 12\. How We Use Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We use cookies and similar tracking technology (collectively, "Cookies") to collect and use personal information about you. For further information about the types of Cookies we use, why, and how you can control Cookies, please see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.mobvoi.com/asia/pages/cookie-policy).

#### 13\. How We Dispose the Personal Information of Children

13.1 Mobvoi's personal and home products are intended for adults. However, for the use of Mobvoi products and services by children, we are fully aware of the importance of taking extra preventive measures to protect privacy and security. Mobvoi identifies whether data subjects are children based on the age of majority defined by laws of the local countries and regions.

13.2 When children's personal information is collected based on the consent of the holders of parental responsibility, we will only use or disclose the information as permitted by law, explicitly consented to by the holders of parental responsibility, or required for protecting the children. Holders of parental responsibility who need to access, modify, or delete the personal information of their children and people under guardianship can contact us via the channels provided in "IV. How Mobvoi Protects Your Personal information."

13.3 If Mobvoi accidentally collects children's personal information without obtaining consent from provable holders of parental responsibility, Mobvoi will delete the information as soon as possible after becoming aware of it.

#### 14\. Privacy Policy Update

14.1 We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on the website and update the "Last Updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy.

14.2 We will give you the opportunity to review the revised Policy before you choose to continue using our Services. If you disagree with the revised Privacy Policy, you may cancel your Account. If you do not cancel your Account before the date the revised Privacy Policy becomes effective, your continued access to or use of the Mobvoi services will be subject to the revised Privacy Policy.

14.3 For the material changes, we may also provide the more prominent notice illustrating the specific changes in the Privacy Policy depending on the circumstances.

14.4 Material changes including but not limited to:

* The material changes in our service mode, such as the purpose of processing personal information, the type of personal information processed and the use of personal information, etc.;
* The material changes in our ownership structure and organization structure, such as owner change due to business adjustment or bankruptcy or merger & acquisition, etc.;
* Changes to the main object in personal information sharing, transfer or public disclosure;
* The material changes in your rights relating to how you are participating in personal information process and ways to exercise such rights;
* The change of responsible department or contact information or complaint channels relating to personal information security reasonability;
* The time of high risk indicated by personal information security assessment report.

#### 15\. How to Contact Us

If you have any inquiry, comments or suggestions about this Privacy Policy or want to discuss this Privacy Policy or any relative, please contact our data protection officer at support@mobvoi.com. The data controller of your personal information is stated at the preamble of this Privacy Policy.

Products & Services

[Mobvoi app](javascript:void(0))

[Ticwear Global app](javascript:void(0))

Referral program

Healthcare

Healthcare

About us

Follow us

Copyright © HK SMARTMV LIMITED. All rights reserved.

[](javascript:void(0))

Help

Help [\-](javascript:void(0))

Please contact official after-sales email: support@mobvoi.com.
